(Amy:)If you don't mind me asking, why
did you and your wife split up?
(Dave:)Oh, you know how it is...
we wanted different things.
(Dave:)I wanted children,
(Dave:)and she wanted a pastry chef
named Jean-Philippe.
(Amy:)Oh, I'm... I'm so sorry.
No, it's-it's fine.
It's why I left England.
(Dave:)It reminded me
too much of her.
(Dave:)Cold, gloomy and easily accessed
by a Frenchman through a tunnel.
(Penny:)Hey. So, where are they?
(Bernadette:)Across the street,
in the left window.
PENNY:
Oh, damn it,
(Penny:)we should have brought
binoculars.
(Bernadette:)Right here.
We just happen to have those
in the car?
(Bernadette:)Kinda. Before I met Howie,
(Bernadette:)I liked to keep close tabs
on my boyfriends.
(Leonard:)By stalking them?
(Bernadette:)No. Stalkers
are creepy.
(Bernadette:)I'm just a harmless little girl
(Bernadette:)with military-grade
spy equipment.
PENNY:
Oh, there he is.
BERNADETTE:
He's cute, right?
Yeah!
Can I see?
(Penny:)What, now you're interested?
You didn't even want to come.
(Leonard:)I know, but you guys make being
a crappy friend look fun.